剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
Desmond说我会死的
Desmond said I was gonna die.
他告诉我他有某种幻觉
He told me he has these flashes... visions.
当我看到闪电击打顶蓬时 你被电死了
When I saw the lightning hit the roof,you were electrocuted.
当你听到Claire溺水时
And when you heard Claire was in the water,
为了救她  你自己却淹死了 我下了水才救了你的命
you drowned trying to save her.I dove in myself, so you never went in.
不管我怎么努力
No matter what I try to do,
你总是要死的 Charlie
you're gonna die, Charlie.
在Hurley的帐篷里有个女人
There's a woman in Hurley's tent
她昨天才跳伞 来到这个岛上
who parachuted onto the island yesterday.
她说她的船就在距离 这里80英里的地方
She says that the boat she took off from is about 80 miles off the coast,
如果她能与那艘船取得联系 我们就得救了
and if she can find a way to contact it,we'll all be rescued.
为什么不告诉我?
Why didn't anyone tell me this?
因为他们不信任你
Because they don't trust you.
Kwon怀孕了
Kwon is pregnant.
你从哪里弄到的?
Where'd you get that?
你以为你有权利 来问我们吗?
You really think you're in a position to ask questions?
我告诉Jack 他们逼我这样做的
I told Jack what they were making me do.
为什么不告诉我们?
Why didn't you tell us?
因为我还不知道 该怎么做
Because I hadn't decided what to do about it yet.
有人知道...
Anyone wants to venture a guess
Jack把我们带到 这荒僻的地方来干什么吗?
as to what Jack's gonna be showing us out in the middle of nowhere?
我也不知道 是看些东西吧
I don't know. Stuff.
也许是秘密的东西
Probably secret stuff.
有必要每件事都保密吗?
Why does everything have to be such a secret?
为什么大家不坦诚一些呢?
How about some openness for a change?
我们为那个跳伞的女人保密
We kept the parachute lady secret.
这个性质不同
Ah, that's different.
怎么不同法?
Different how?
因为我们可没有 到那里去和他们"踢足球"
Well, because we weren't out there playing football with them.
怎么了?
What?
没什么
Nothing.
等等
Wait.
你又有幻觉了是吗?
You had one of your flashes again,didn't you?
不  Charlie  没有
No, Charlie, I didn't.
我们到了
We're here.
几天前...
A couple of nights ago,
Juliet告诉了我所有的事...
Juliet came to me,and she told me everything...
Ben让她来找出 我们这里的孕妇
That Ben had sent her here to find out which of our women were pregnant.
那你们想在我们身上做实验咯?
So what, you guys were doing tests on us?
不  但他要我这样做
No, but that's what he wanted me to do.
我把磁带 留在那个医疗站里
I've been leaving tapes at the medical station.
你们都听见他说的了
You all heard what he said.
他们明天就来
They're coming tomorrow.
Sun 很抱歉对你撒了谎
Sun, I'm sorry that I lied to you.
我很感激你的坦诚 Jack
While I appreciate your honesty, Jack,
但这也不能解释为什么 把我们带来这里
it doesn't explain why you brought us out here.
Danielle
让他们瞧瞧
Show'em.
当Juliet告诉我 他们要来时
When Juliet told me they where coming,
我想到的第一件事就是...
the first thing I thought was,
这次我们又要往哪儿躲?
where the hell are we gonna hide this time?
躲躲藏藏是没用的
But hiding's pointless.
他们还会不断的回来
They're just gonna keep coming back.
所以我出去寻求帮助
So I went out, and I found some help.
在这几天里
And for the past few days,
她一直从"黑岩"那边 搬炸药回来
she's been bringing dynamite back from "the black rock."
难得这一次...
For the very first time,
我们知道他们想要什么 他们什么时候会来
we know exactly what they want,when they're coming to get it,
而且他们还蒙在鼓里
and they have no idea
我们会在这里等着他们
that we're gonna be waiting for'em.
Juliet会按照原来的指示
So Juliet's gonna mark the tents
用白色的石头给帐篷做标记
with the white rocks,just like she was told to,
但里面不会有孕妇
but there's not gonna be any pregnant women inside.
里面有的是我们 用在那颗树上的东西
There's gonna be plenty of what we used on that tree.
明天晚上...
So tomorrow night...
我们不再躲藏
We stop hiding.
我们不再逃跑
We stop running.
我们不再生活在恐惧之中 因为当他们出现时...
We stop living in fear of them,because when they show up...
我们会把他们炸上天
we're gonna blow'em all to hell.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：   许愿  后期：梁良  双语字幕：七色九天
该死的!
Bloody hell!
我们干嘛要这样做?
Why are we even doing this?
冷静点  老兄
Chin up, mate.
-我们在做宣传   -宣传?
-We're headlining.   -Headlining?
我们要在Clitheroe演出...
We're playing Clitheroe...
这里又是哪里?
The arse end of nowhere.
演出是演出
A gig's a gig.
可我们得发展我们的歌迷
We're building our fan base.
我们的歌迷会给我们 买个新轮胎吗?
Will our fan base pay for a new sodding tire?
只有当我们 出现在公众场合
Only if we show up.
所以我们还是走吧  好吗?
So let's just get on with it, shall we?
你知道吗 Liam?
You know what, Liam?
你去吧
You get on with it.
我不干了
I quit.
-你就这样放弃了吗?    -我们根本没什么可放弃的!
-You're giving up?   -There's nothing to give up on!
我们破产了  专辑根本卖不出去! 我们只是个笑话!
We're broke! The album's not selling! We're a bloody joke!
都闭嘴!
Hey, shut it!
听
Listen.
那是我们
That's us.
我们上电台了!
We're on the radio!
那是我们
That we are.
我们他妈的上电台了!
We're on the bloody radio!
我告诉过你  兄弟!
I told you, baby brother!
我们会成为摇滚明星的
We're gonna be bloody rock stars.
能问你个问题吗?
Can I ask you something?
你们在向谁开战?
Who are you people about to go to war with?
说来话长
Oh, that's a long story.
还想问我什么?
Want to ask me something else?
你在笑吗?
You having a laugh?
当然不是
Of course not.
我绝不会不尊重 曼彻斯特同胞的
I'd never disrespect a fellow Mancunian.
-你是曼彻斯特的咯?   -是啊
-You're from Manchester, then?   -I am.
我们的乐队是从Oldham大街上的 一个酒吧开始的
My band got its start at the night and day bar on Oldham street.
-什么乐队?      -我们叫它"Drive Shaft"
-What band?     -We were called Drive Shaft.
是啊  我认识你
Yeah. Yeah, I know you.
我们有过一段辉煌的日子
We had our moment in the sun.
不  不是那个...是坠机
No, not that... the crash.
你是那个死了的 摇滚巨星
You're the dead rock star.
他们找到飞机后 就开始宣传这件事
They made a big deal out of you when they found the plane.
什么纪念活动啦 新唱片啦
Huge memorial service, new album.
还有新唱片?
There's a new album?
到处都有卖...
Yeah. God, it was everywhere...
还是"精选集"来着
A "greatest hits" thing.
往好的方面去想
Hey, look on the bright side.
你没有真死  对吗?
You're not really dead, right?
是啊
Yeah, right.
我们需要更多的导线
We need more wire,
以便于能在 安全的距离引爆
so we can trigger these from a safe distance.
我可以叫他们去 飞机残骸那找找
I can get people to start stripping the plane wreckage.
很好  我们应该在24小时内
Good. I should be able to finish rigging these tents
把帐篷都布置好
in the next 24 hours.
为明晚做好充分的准备
We'll be ready by tomorrow night.
我们得谈谈Naomi电话的事
We need to talk about Naomi's phone.
-不是现在    -如果你因为我怀疑你而生气
-Not now.    -If you're angry I doubted you,
等等我会向你道歉的
I'd be happy to make a sincere apology later,
-但现在我们有...     -我现在很忙
-but now we have a means...    -Look, I'm a little bit busy right now.
我努力想让大家都得救!
And I am trying to get us off this island!
我不能往外发信号
I can't transmit using this phone
因为Danielle的求救信号 阻隔了我们的信号
because Danielle's distress signal is overriding the frequency.
如果你能带我们去 那个无线电塔
If you tell me where the radio tower is,
我就能把你的信号关掉 然后发出求救信号
I can go there, switch off your message and call for help.
我的信号 已经播放了16年了
My signal has been playing for the last 16 years,
但谁都没收到
and nobody has heard it.
你怎么肯定 你的运气比我更好?
Why do you think you'll have better luck?
Naomi的船就在80英里外
Naomi's boat is only 80 miles offshore.
我相信只要关闭Danielle的信号 他们就能听到我们
I know if we eliminate Danielle's signal, they'll hear us.
不  他们不会的
No, they won't.
怎么会?
And why is that?
都是我们在阻挠
We're jamming it.
什么?
What?
Ben在使用一个达摩的站
Ben is using one of the Dharma stations
来阻挠除了我们 所有发出岛的信号
to block all of the signals off of the island except for ours.
那是什么站?
What station?
他们叫它"守望镜"
They call it the "Looking Glass."
-守望镜?    -是的
-The looking glass?    -Yes.
但那在海底 我也不知道在哪儿
But it's underwater.I have no idea where it is.
我想我知道
I believe I do.
我知道Jack总不会错的
Look, I know...I know Jack thinks it's best,
但他们来找他怎么办?
but, you know, what if they're coming for him again?
Claire 听我说
Claire, listen to me.
我会保护你的
I'm gonna protect you.
我会保护Aaron
I'm gonna protect Aaron.
我保证
I promise.
一切都会好起来的
Look, everything is gonna be fine.
抱歉
Sorry.
Charlie 能帮下忙吗?
Can you give me a hand with something?
当然 Desmond
yeah,Desmond,Of course.
你可以说你今天早上 看到什么了吗?
So you ready to tell me what you saw this morning?
好吧
Aye.
这次又会发生什么?
Right. So how does it happen this time?
说啊 Des!
Come on, Des!
你可以告诉我 我能接受的
You can tell me. I can take it.
我看见的...Charlie  是...
What I saw, Charlie, was...
Claire和她的宝宝 登上了直升机...
Claire and her baby getting into a helicopter...
那个直升机...
A helicopter that...
从这座岛上起飞了
That lifts off, leaves this island.
你确定吗?
You sure?
是的
Aye.
救援飞机...
Rescue helicopter...
在这个海滩?
On this beach?
这个岛?  你看见了吗?
This island? That's what you saw?
我们都得救了!
We're getting bloody rescued!
我还以为我又会死了呢!
I thought you were gonna tell me I was gonna die again.
是的 Charlie
You are, Charlie.
等等  你说什么?
Wait. What?
如果你不死的话...
If you don't...
这些就都不会发生
None of it will happen.
不会有什么救援
There won't be any rescue.
我很抱歉  老兄...
I'm sorry, brother...
但这一次...
but this time...
你必须得死
This time you have to die.
来啊!
Come on!
来啊 Charlie  跳进来!
Come on, Charlie. Jump in!
我会接着你的  孩子
I'm gonna catch you, boy.
不  你会松手的
No. You're just going to back away.
别傻了  跳进来啊!
Don't be daft. Jump in!
我保证 Charlie  我会接着你的
I promise, Charlie. I'm gonna catch you.
不  他不会的!
No, he won't!
你给我闭嘴
Zip it, you.
别听你兄弟瞎说
Look, don't listen to your brother.
跳进来吧
Just jump on in.
没什么好害怕的 Charlie
There's nothing to be afraid of,Charlie.
我保证会接着你的
I'll catch you. I promise.
我做到了!
I did it!
你做到了!
You got it!
-我做到了     -你在游泳 Charlie
-I did it.      -You're swimming, Charlie.
你在写什么?
What you writing?
没什么
Nothing.
好吧  告诉我
All right, tell me.
你确定吗?
Are you sure you want to know?
如果那样会好受点...
I mean, it might be easier if you just...
我想知道
I want to know.
你在一个舱里
You're inside a hatch.
那里...
It's...
有很多仪器设备
a room full of equipment.
有个闪着黄灯的开关
There's a blinking yellow light above a switch.
你扳动了开关
You flip the switch.
灯就灭了
Light goes off.
然后你就被淹死了
And then you drown.
在什么时候?
When?
我也不知道
I don't know.
你确定看见Claire和Aaron 登上直升机了吗?
You're sure you saw Claire and Aaron get on that helicopter?
是的
Aye.
那么...
So...
在我淹死之前
before I... drown...
我就扳了那个开关?
I just have to flip a switch?
是这样的
That's right.
那个地方在哪里?
Where is it, then?
这就是"守望镜"
Now this is the Looking Glass.
是一个水下的达摩站
It's an underwater Dharma station.
能告诉我你所知道的吗?
Please, can you tell me anything you might know about this place?
我从来没下去过
I've never been down there.
我也不知道谁下去过
I don't know anyone who has.
怎么会?
Why not?
因为发生了意外
There was some accident.
Ben告诉我们那个站 已经被淹了
Ben told us that the station was completely flooded.
如果被淹了 怎么还能工作?
Well, if it's flooded,then how does it still work?
怎么工作的并不重要
How it still works is irrelevant.
问题在于我们怎么下去 让它停止工作
The question is, how do we get it to stop working,
然后用我们的卫星电话
so we could use the satellite phone?
这张图表示"守望镜"
The diagram shows that the Looking Glass
和这座岛 以一根电缆相连
is connected to the island by a cable.
我相信这和那根...
I feel sure that this is the very same cable
深入海里的电缆是同一条
down the beach which runs into the ocean.
所以我们顺着这条电缆 就能找到那个站
So if we follow the cable,it should lead us to the station.
那我们怎么进去?
So how are we gonna get in?
游泳进去
We swim in.
那里有个小潭...
There's a moon pool...
在站下有个地面敞开的房间...
A room with an open floor at the base of the station...
大到能让一艘 潜艇停泊
Big enough for a submarine to dock.
即使站已经被淹了
Even if the station's flooded,
我想还是有办法找到开关 来解除阻隔信号
I think I'll be able to find the relay switch and disable it.
那怎么游出来呢?
What about swimming back out?
我不会让你去执行 什么自杀任务的
No. I'm not letting you go on some suicide mission
只是扳个开关
just to flip the switch.
总要有人去做 否则我们永远别想离开这里
Someone has to do it,or we'll never leave this island.
我来吧
I'll do it.
我能游下去  扳下那个开关 然后游上来
I can swim down, turn off that bloody switch, swim back up.
小菜一碟
Piece of cake.
Charlie你根本不知道 我们在说什么
Charlie, you don't even know what we're talking about.
我可是北英格兰 少年组游泳冠军
I was junior swim champion in northern England.
我闭气能达到4分钟
I can hold my breath for 4 minutes.
我知道你们在说什么
I know exactly what you're talking about.
不  现在我们还没必要做这个
No, and there's no reason to do this now.
我们得把精力放在"the others"上 然后再来处理这件事
We're gonna focus on the others,and then we'll deal with this.
等等 我们有机会发信号出去
Wait a minute.We have a chance to signal for a rescue.
90天来大家都要我 做出决定
Look, for 90 days, I've been asked to make decisions for this entire camp.
很好  我刚就做了一个
There you go.I just made one.
Rose 那是个"水手结"
Rose, that's a sailor's hitch.
绑不紧的 你要像我这样弯一下
It's not gonna hold.You wanna do a sheet bend like mine.
那你是个打结专家咯?
Oh, so now you're a knot expert.
相信我  这...
Well, trust me, it's...
你是怎么做到的?
How did you do that?
边观察边学习  亲爱的
Watch and learn, dear.
你要等到什么时候 才告诉我?
拜托了 Sun
我听见Juliet的磁带上 有你我的名字
大家都看着你
是怀孕的事吗?
我看见我们的孩子了
在超声波仪器里
Juliet带我去了那个医疗站
而且她...
孩子还好吗?
非常非常的健康
看那边! 看啊!
Look there! Look!
该死的  放开他! 没关系的
Get off him, damn it! It's okay.
-什么?  他是他们的人!    -我知道  没关系的!
-What? He's one of them!   -I know! It's okay.
他被关在我旁边 的笼子里
He was in the cage next to me.
我认识这家伙
I know this guy.
你来这里干什么 Karl?
What the hell are you doing here, Karl?
他们...来了...
They're... coming...
我的人
My people.
抱歉你大老远的过来白说一通 我们已经知道了
Sorry you came all this way for nothing,but we already know.
那你们为什么还在这里?
Then why are you still here?
因为当他们明晚来的时候 我们会做好充分的准备
'cause when they'll show up tomorrow night, we're gonna be ready for'em.
明天?  不不 他们今晚就来!
Tomorrow? No, no,they're coming tonight.
他们现在就来了!
They're coming right now!
6小时前...
你什么时候回来的?
When did you get back?
就刚才
Just now.
Locke在哪里?
Where's Locke?
这把枪还你
Here's your gun back.
Ben 发生什么事了?
Ben, what's going on?
Ryan在哪里?
Where's Ryan?
在他的帐篷里  你...
He's in his tent. Are you...
是时候行动了
It's time to get them.
但你说是明天
But you said tomorrow.
这是Jacob的决定
Jacob wants it to happen now.
那里发生了什么事?
Look, what happened out there?
-John有没有看到...  -John发生了意外
-Did john see...     -John had an accident.
Ryan?
是?
Yes, sir?
如果你们现在就出发
If you leave right now,
到他们的营地要多久?
how long will it take you to reach their camp?
如果我带上我的10个精英 黄昏就能发起攻击
Well,if I take my ten best,we could set up to hit'em by nightfall.
-那你们最好现在就出发    -Ben等一下
-Then you better get going.    -No, Ben, wait.
改变计划...
Moving up the schedule...
Juliet也许还没准备好 如果她没有时间...
Juliet may not be ready.What if she hasn't had time...
那我们就把所有的女人 都带走...
Then we'll take all their women...
然后再找出我们想要的
And we'll sort out the ones we need later.
男人呢?
And the men?
如果他们挡你的道的话
If any of'em are stupid enough to get in your way,
杀了他们
kill'em.
好吧
All right.
Karl!
是我!
It's me!
还以为你带兔子来了
I thought you were bringing rabbit.
你现在就得走
You have to go... now.
什么  他发现我在这里了吗?
What? Did he find out I was out here?
不  但他已经派Pryce 去他们的营地了
No, but he's sending Pryce to their beach camp right now,
你必须去警告他们
and you have to warn them.
-警告他们?    -你必须现在就去!
-Warn them?     -You have to go now!
我以为他们只是去 抓孕妇
I thought they were just gonna take the pregnant women.
如果你坐木筏去
If you take the outrigger,
你就能在他们之前到那儿
you'll get there a few hours before them.
-等等 Alex...  -他会杀光他们的 Karl!
-Wait, Alex...   -He's gonna kill them Karl!
Austen和Ford救了你的命
Austen and Ford saved your life.
你欠他们的
You owe them.
最好带上这个
You better take this.
如果我这次被抓住 你爸爸会杀了我的
If I get caught, your father's gonna kill me this time.
他是我爸爸吗?
Is he my father?
快走
Now go.
就这些了吗?
Is that everything?
我们能相信他吗?
Can we trust him?
你不相信我?
You don't trust me?
那她呢?
What about her?
她是个间谍
She's a spy.
她会在孕妇帐篷外 用白色石头做标记的
She's supposed to mark the tents of the pregnant women with white rocks
-那样他们能带走他们     -他们都知道了 Karl  但还是谢谢
-so they can take them.    -They know, Karl, but thanks.
-那我们现在怎么办?    -我们必须现在就走...躲起来
-So what are we gonna do?   -We have to leave now... Hide.
去哪儿?  这是他们的岛 他们想杀我们就一定能找到我们
Where? It's their island. If they wanna kill us,they'll find us.
几小时后就日落了
The sun's gonna go down in a few hours.
-我的导线准备的怎样了?   -还差的很远
-Do we have enough wire yet?    -Not even close.
我们必须另想办法 来引爆炸药
We have to find out another way to set the dynamite off.
-我们能用枪打   -我们没有足够的枪
-We can shoot.   -We don't have enough guns.
他们有10个人 都带着武器
Ten of them are coming, armed.
不是"the others"... 是帐篷
Not the others... the tents.
我们把炸药隐藏 在帐篷的旁边
We can camouflage the dynamite next to the tents,
我们能在树林里 瞄准它们
target it from our positions at the tree line.
Juliet给3个帐篷做了标记 我们需要3把枪
Juliet marked three tents.That means we need three guns.
拿着  我的也给你们
Here. You can have mine, too.
我是第3个
I'll be your third.
我们会拿走你的枪 但你必须离开这里
I'll take your gun,but you're not staying here.
你要带领每一个人 去无线电塔
You're gonna lead everyone to the radio tower... Everyone.
无线电塔?
The radio tower?
如果行动失败的话 我们不能冒险失去
If this doesn't work,we can't risk losing the chance
可以联络到Naomi的船的机会
of getting in contact with Naomi's boat,
每件事必须同时进行
so everything has to happen at the same time.
你还想去游泳吗?
You still up for a swim?
是啊  当然愿意
Yeah, I believe I am.
我和他一起去
I'll go with him.
好了  大家行动起来
Okay, better get to it.
来了  小兄弟
It's here, baby brother.
圣诞节来了
Christmas is here.
这两个是第2排的吧?
Are these the birds from row two?
干的好  兄弟
Well done, mate.
你用了1年的时间...
Well, as you have spent another year
作为世界上唯一一个 不吸毒的摇滚巨星
as the only drug-free rock star in the world,
我来跟你说说 一个鲜为人知的事实
I'm gonna share a little-known fact with you.
圣诞老人就住这条街上
Father christmas lives just down the street from here.
圣诞老人住在Helsinki?
Father christmas lives in Helsinki?
的确是这样
Indeed he does,
以防你没有注意到
and in case you haven't noticed,baby brother,
芬兰其实就是北极
Finland is the bloody north pole.
我有个很特别的 圣诞礼物要送给你
Therefore, I have a very special gift for you this year.
Liam 不  这是妈妈给你的
Liam, no. Mum gave you that.
你是大哥
You're the firstborn.
这是她父亲的父亲的...
It was her father's and his father before that.
这是祖上传下来的 所以我们命名我们的乐队为
And it's a family heirloom,and that's why we named the band
Dexter Stratton
after Dexter bloody Stratton.
我知道
I know.
但Charlie  老实说
But, Charlie, let's be honest.
我们都知道我是个没出息的
We both know I'm a sodding mess.
但你...和我不同
But you... You're different.
你会结婚 拥有自己的家庭...
You're gonna get married,have a family...
一个孩子
A baby.
到我30时会时来运转的
I'll be lucky if I hit 30.
别这么说 Lee
Don't say that, Lee.
这枚戒指必须 留在家族里 Charlie
The ring has to stay in the family, Charlie.
所以拜托...
So, please...
收下吧
Take it.
妈妈希望这样
Mum would have wanted it this way.
有一天你也会传下去的
Pass it on to your little one someday.
你要保管好它
I need to know it's safe.
我会保管好的...
I'll hold on to it...
但我不会收下的
but I won't take it.
-刚刚好   -看啊
-Hey, it fits.   -Look at that.
圣诞快乐  小兄弟
Happy christmas, baby brother.
需要帮助吗?
You need some help?
为什么不告诉我 你要这样做?
Why didn't you tell me you were gonna do this?
我不想让你担心
I didn't want you to worry.
很危险是吗?
Well, it's dangerous, isn't it,
潜水去海底的什么站?
swimming into some underwater station?
只有这样做我们 才能得救
It's what needs to be done to get us all rescued.
我会没事的 Claire
I'll be fine, Claire.
但你得保证我...
But you gotta promise me something.
等我走了...
While I'm gone...
别为我担心
Don't worry about me.
我来抱抱他
I'll take him.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了  可爱头
Alright, turnip head.
等我走了
Now you take care of your mum
照顾好你妈妈
while I'm away, okay?
我爱你
I love you.
再见
See you soon.
小心 Charlie
Be careful, Charlie.
好吗?
Okay?
抱歉
Sorry, guys.
谢谢
Thanks, man.
救救我  救救我!
Help! Help me!
求你了!
Please!
你  停下!
You, stop!
离她远点!
Get the hell away from her!
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
离她远点!
Leave her alone!
你还好吗  女士?
You okay, miss?
我想是的
Yes. I think so, yes.
这个给你
Here you go.
抱歉我"心脏病"又犯了
Pardon me while I have a heart attack.
上次打架还是在8岁的时候
The last time I was in a fight,I was 8 years old.
还输了
And I lost.
你是个英雄 你知道吗?
Well, that makes you even more of a hero, doesn't it?
换作别人也会这样做的
I just did what anyone would do.
3个人路过这里
Three people walked by the alley.
-什么?   -他们看见我了
-What?    -They saw me,
但他们还是继续赶路
but they just kept on going.
你是个英雄  先生...
You are a hero, sir...
请你不要怀疑这一点
And don't let anyone ever tell you differently.
第五 第一次在电台里听到自己的歌
第四 老爸在Butlins教我游泳
第三 圣诞节Liam把家传戒指作为礼物 送了给我
第二 修女院外的一个女人称我为 英雄
-那是什么?    -重量带
-What's that?   -It's a weight belt.
它能很快把你带到那里
It should bring you down quicker than swimming.
每秒都很重要
Well, every second counts.
那么我到了海底就松开它们
So I just take it off when I hit bottom,
然后游到那个小潭
swim up through the moon pool,
进入那个站
into the station,
找到一个有黄灯的开关
swim into whichever room has the yellow blinking switch,
然后扳一下
flip it.
就这么简单?
Nothing to it.
你能闭气多久?
So how long can you really hold your breath for?
这还重要吗?
Does it matter?
-想要我再打一个吗?   -不  我想你能做到
-Do you want me to hit another one?    -No,you've made your point.
Bernard这不是在 Montgomery的乡村打野鸡
Bernard, this is not pheasant hunting in Montgomery county.
-我知道自己在干什么    -不
-I know what I'm doing.   -No,you don't
-野鸡是不会还击的     -我不会有事的 Rose
-Pheasants don't shoot back.    -Nothing's gonna happen to me, Rose.
我只需打中帐篷 我会跟上你们的
I just have to shoot a tent,and I'll be right behind you.
那我也留下
Then I'm staying, too.
不  你不能 Rose
No, you're not, Rose.
大家都集中在海滩的南头
Everyone's gathering down at the south end of the beach.
除了枪手 其他人必须离开
No one's staying behind but the shooters.
谁说的?  你必须保证...
Says who? You wanna give me your word
我丈夫会没事的 那我才走
that nothing's gonna happen to my husband, then I'll go.
我保证你 如果接下来的1小时里
I'll give you my word that if we don't kill everyone
我们还没有杀光他们
who shows up here in about an hour,
Bernard马上就能离开
it's not gonna matter where Bernard is.
我更喜欢回来后的Jack
I like you better since you got back, Jack.
你都成乐观主义者了
You're almost an optimist.
来吧  如果你要躲在丛林里
Come on.If you're gonna be hiding in the bushes,
我们帮你藏好了
let's get you into somethin'dark.
你该走了
You better get going.
Rousseau说去那个无线电站 要一天的时间
Rousseau says it's about a day's walk up to the radio tower.
我不带他们去 你去吧
I'm not taking them to the tower.You are.
-你说什么?    -你不能留在这里
-Excuse me?     -You're not staying behind.
这是我的主意
This was my idea.
我能完成这个任务
And I'm perfectly capable of executing it.
-我欠他们的!  -你更关心什么?
-I owe them!   -What are you more concerned with,
杀了"the others"还是 帮助我们离开这座岛?
killing the others or getting our people off this island?
今天下午你说你是个领袖
This afternoon,you said you were our leader.
是时候表现出领袖的样子了
It's time for you to act like one.
带他们去无线电站 Jack...
Lead them to the radio tower, Jack...
然后带我们回家
and then take us all home.
伙计  等等!
Dudes, wait!
我听说了你们要去干嘛 我想一起来
I heard what you're doing.I wanna come with.
大家都去那个无线电站了
Everyone...They're all going to the radio tower,
我厌倦了长途旅行 还有爆炸...
and I'm sick of trekking and,you know, explosions.
我想我能帮上你们的忙
I think I can help you guys out.
我很在行划浆
I'm a really good paddler.
你不能去 Hurley
You can't go, Hurley.
为什么?
Why not?
因为...
Because...
你个头太大了
you're too big.
装不进船里
You won't fit in the boat.
真不走运
That's uncool, man.
等等
Wait.
伙计没事的   我也不想坐这傻船
Dude, it's fine. I don't even wanna go on your stupid boat.
我们一会儿再见
I'll catch up with you later.
我爱你  兄弟
Just remember I love you, man.
随便啦  我也爱你
Yeah, whatever. I love you, too.
水灌好了吗?  好  好
You got water in there? Good, good.
你呢?  灌好了吗?
How about you? Bottled water?
好
Good.
又要开始了吗?
So here we go again, huh?
又要开始了
Here we go again.
帐篷都做上标记了 我们准备好了
The tents are all marked. We're set.
Sayid找到第3个人了吗?
Sayid find the third shooter?
准备好了吗 Claire? 要我帮帮你的宝宝吗?
Ready, Claire? Need a hand with the little guy?
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks. I'm okay.
我的小甜心怎么了?
How's my little sweetheart?
我们只是要赶些路 抱紧妈妈  好吗?
We're just gonna go for a little walk,so hold onto mum, okay?
就这里了!
This is it!
准备好了吗?
Ready?
需要毯子吗?
Do you want a blanket?
谢谢  我已经有了
Oh, thanks. I've got one.
不是还有你宝宝吗?
Well, you're warming for two.
把我的拿去吧
Take mine.
谢谢
Thank you.
第一次坠机吧?
So... first plane crash?
你怎么知道?
What gave it away?
新手我第一眼就能看出来
Ah, you can always spot the newbies.
我们会没事的
We're gonna be okay, you know.
是吗?
Are we?
我们至少还活着
We're alive.
在这美丽的小岛上
We're on a beautiful island.
沉睡在星空里
We'll sleep under the stars,
不知不觉中 直升机会带我们离开这座岛的
and before you know it,the helicopters will come and take us all home.
你相信他们能找到我们?
You really think they'll find us?
为什么不呢?
Well, yeah. Why wouldn't they?
谢谢
Thanks.
我叫Charlie
I'm Charlie.
我叫Claire
I'm Claire.
很高兴见到你 Charlie
Nice to meet you, Charlie.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
第一 遇到你的那个晚上
我们到了
We're here.
我希望你能把这个交给Claire
I want you to give this to Claire for me.
这是什么?
What is it?
我愧疚的一生中...
It's the five best moments of my...
5个最重要的时刻
sorry excuse for a life.
我的"精选集"
My greatest hits.
你知道...
You know...
回忆...
memories...
就是我的全部
are all I've got.
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
什么?
What?
我来代替你
I'll go.
不  你的幻觉...
No, your... Your flashes...
也许...
Maybe...
我一直看见你死...
I keep seeing you die because...
是因为我注定要 替代你的位置
I'm supposed to take your place.
你的女朋友怎么办...
What about your girl...
Penny?
那你的女朋友呢?
What about your girl?
还有...
Besides...
我的运气也许比你要好
I might be luckier than you.
留着你的回忆
Keep your memories to yourself.
我从这里下去
I'll take it from here.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
你可以告诉我重量带在哪里?
Well, you can tell me where the,the weight belt is.
就在你后面
Right there behind you.
你我都知道...
You and I both know...
你不该代替我的  兄弟
You aren't supposed to take my place, brother.
我还活着!
I'm alive.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■